So, just as was the case with mark-and-sweep, when we scan an object, we
因此，就像标记和扫掠一样，当我们扫描对象时，我们
have to know how big it is and we also need to know where the pointers and the
必须知道它有多大，我们还需要知道指针和
object are. So, if we think about this for a minute, let's say we're scanning this
对象是。所以，如果我们想一分钟，比方说我们正在扫描这个
object, so this is our scan pointer and we want now to process all the pointers in
对象，因此这是我们的扫描指针，我们现在要处理
it, well, we have to know where the pointers are. So, there's a pointer here
它，嗯，我们必须知道指针在哪里。所以，这里有一个指针
and there's a pointer here and we'll be able to find those pointers and we don't
这里有一个指针，我们可以找到这些指针，但是我们不能
want to confuse them with other fields of the object that might look like pointers.
我希望将它们与对象的其他字段混淆，这些字段可能看起来像指针。
So, in a bit pattern for an integer could look an awful lot like a pointer. Now,
因此，在位模式中，整数可能看起来非常像指针。现在,
this is not a big problem because the compiler, of course, in terms of, a lot of
这不是一个大问题，因为编译器，当然，在很多方面
the objects in the heap and it can stor e that information somewhere communicated to
堆中的对象，它可以将该信息存储在与之通信的某个位置
the garbage collector so that it will be able to find the pointers. So, you can
垃圾收集器，以便它能够找到指针。所以，你可以
imagine easily a little bit of information stored with the program indicating for
可以很容易地想象一下与程序一起存储的一点信息，该程序指示
each type where the pointers are. And similarly once we've scanned this object,
指针所在的每种类型。同样，一旦我们扫描了这个物体，
we need to be able to advance our scan pointer just past the object so that we
我们需要能够使扫描指针刚好经过对象，以便我们
can find the beginning of the next object and that's why we need to know the size,
可以找到下一个物体的开头，这就是为什么我们需要知道它的大小，
okay. So, we need to know that size so that the scan pointer can be moved past
好吧。因此，我们需要知道该大小，以便可以将扫描指针移过
the object and we can find the beginning of the next object. Another issue is that
然后我们就可以找到下一个对象的开头。另一个问题是，
whenever we do a garbage collection, I haven't mentioned this up to this point
每当我们进行垃圾收集时，到目前为止我还没有提到过这一点
but it should be clear, we also have to scan and copy objects pointed to by the
但是应该清楚的是，我们还必须扫描和复制
stack. And we also have to update pointers in the stack. And this can actually turn
堆栈。我们还必须更新堆栈中的指针。而这实际上可以变成
out to be kind of an expensive operation with stop-and-copy because, you know, you
停印是一种昂贵的操作，因为，你知道，你
still have to walk the entire stack each time you do a collection in order to make
仍然必须遍历整个堆栈，以便在每次收集时
sure that you've copied all the objects pointed to by the stack. To conclude
确保您已经复制了堆栈指向的所有对象。最后，我要总结一下
stop-and-copy, I think it's fair to say, is generally believed to be the fastest
我认为，公平地说，停机复制通常被认为是最快的
garbage collection technique. Certainly, I believe that variations on stop-and- copy
垃圾收集技术。当然，我相信停印和复印的变体
are the most efficient approaches known to automatic memory management. Allocation is
是已知的自动内存管理最有效的方法。分配是
very cheap, alright. So, cuz all you have to do is increment the e-pointer. So,
很便宜，好吧。所以，因为你所要做的就是递增电子指针。所以,
you're just moving a, a, single pointer forward to allocate space. There's no
你只是向前移动一个，一个，一个指针来分配空间。没有
complicated free list future verse or decisions to make about where to put the
复杂的自由列表未来的诗句或决定放在哪里
object, you know, you're just going to allocate it directly at the allocation
对象，您知道，您只需在分配时直接分配它
pointer. So, you know, this, this part of memory management is, is very inexpensive.
指针。所以你知道这-这部分内存管理是非常便宜的。
And at the same time, collection is also relatively cheap. And, and interestingly
同时，收藏也相对便宜。而且，有趣的是
it's especially cheap if there is a lot of garbage because, because of making a copy
如果有很多垃圾的话就特别便宜了，因为因为复印
of the reachable objects stop-and-copy only touches the reac hable object, It is
在可访问对象中，停止并复制仅涉及可访问对象，它是
not, in particular, does not touch the garbage. So, if you think about that for a
不，特别是不碰垃圾。所以，如果你考虑一下这一点
minute, that means that the garbage collection is in stop-and-copy is order
分钟，这意味着垃圾收集是按停止复制的顺序进行的
the size of the live objects. So, whatever the sub-graph is that you're copying,
活动对象的大小。所以，不管你复制的是什么子图，
that's the cost of a garbage collection and that's in contrast to mark-and-sweep
这是垃圾收集的成本，这与标记和清除形成对比
were the cost is proportional to all the memory that you're using cuz you have the
成本与您正在使用的所有内存成正比，因为您拥有
sweep phase where you have to go through and touch every single object whether it's
扫描阶段，您必须通过并触摸每个单独的对象，无论是
live or garbage, okay. And so, if you have a relatively lot of garbage and a
活着还是垃圾，好的。因此，如果你有相对较多的垃圾和
relatively small set of live objects, stop-and-copy is actually much, much
相对较小的一组活动对象，停止和复制实际上是非常多的
faster than mark-and-sweep. Now, of course the down side of stop-and-copy is that it
比标记和清扫更快。现在，停止复制的缺点当然是它
moves the objects in some languages, in particular C and C++, can't allow you to
在某些语言中移动对象，特别是C和C++，不允许您
move objects because the address that which an object lives is actually visible
移动对象，因为对象所在的地址实际上是可见的
exposed in the program and is part of the semantics of the object. And so there, you
在程序中公开，是对象语义的一部分。所以在那里，你
really have to use mark-and-sweep because you're not allowed to move anything.
真的必须使用标记和清扫，因为你不允许移动任何东西。